Elmo Roper Papers
© 2002 University of Connecticut
- Series III: Speeches, Notes and Polls, undated, 1936-1969
  - Speech cards,1939-
    - Public Opinion Research, 1943 January 4 (Box 35:2214)
    - "The Public Looks at Big Business," Boston Conference on Distribution, 1943 October 19 (Box 35:2215)
    - Advertising Women's Club, ca. 1943-1946 (Box 35:2216)
    - American Jewelers, 1944 August 22 (Box 35:2217)
    - "The Present Mood of the American Public," Financial Advertisers Association, 1945 March 13 (Box 35:2218)
    - Pelham Memorial High School, 1945 March 28 (Box 35:2219)
    - Urban League, 1945 April 9 (Box 35:2220)
    - American Meat Institute Annual Meeting, 1945 October 30 (Box 35:2221)
    - American Municipal Association, 1945 November 15 (Box 35:2222)
    - "Some Problems Americans are Thinking About," Standard Oil Public Relations, 1945 November 19 (Box 35:2223)
    - B'nai B'rith, 1945 November 23 (Box 35:2224)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1945 November 29 (Box 35:2225)
    - "The Power of Information," Sales Executive Club of New York, 1946 February 5 (Box 35:2226)
    - "Determining Employee Attitudes and Opinions," Training Directors Conference, 1946 March 7 (Box 35:2227)
    - "Some Problems Americans are Thinking About," Advertising Women, 1946 March 25 (Box 35:2228)
    - American Association of Advertising Agencies, 1946 April 11 (Box 35:2229)
    - "The Climate of Public Opinion," New Jersey League pf Women Voters, 1946 May 14 (Box 35:2230)
    - Student Federalists, 1946 September 4 (Box 35:2231)
    - "A Survey of Attitudes Towards Casualty and Surety Insurance," Association of Casualty and Surety Executives, 1946 October (Box 35:2232)
    - "What the Public Thinks," 1946 October 8 (Box 35:2233)
    - Tea Association, 1946 october 14 (Box 35:2234)
    - Anti-Defamation League--Women's Division, 1946 October 21 (Box 35:2235)
    - "The Climate of American Public Opinion," Standard Oil Public Relations, 1946 December 2 (Box 35:2236)
    - "America One Year After the War", ca. 1946 (Box 35:2237)
    - Advertising Women, 1947 March 31 (Box 35:2238)
    - Freedom House, 1947 April 4 (Box 35:2239)
    - "Public Opinion Polls--Panacea or Peril?" Market Research Council, 1947 April 18 (Box 35:2240)
    - Freedom House, 1947 May 28 (Box 35:2241)
    - University of Louisville, 1947 September 20 (Box 35:2242)
    - "The High Cost of Discrimination in Business," 1947 November 11 (Box 35:2243)
    - Ford Presentation, 1947 December 2 (Box 35:2244)
    - "The Research Man Looks at 1948," Radio Executives, 1948 January 28 (Box 35:2245)
    - "The High Cost of Discrimination," Urban League, 1948 February 12 (Box 35:2246)
    - Wilkie Anniversary, Freedom House, 1948 February 18 (Box 35:2247)
    - O'Dwyer Citation, National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1948 February 25 (Box 35:2248)
    - Young Republicans, 1948 February 26 (Box 35:2249)
    - "the Importance of Education to Public Opinion," Danbury Women, 1948 March 21 (Box 35:2250)
    - "The Road to Peace," Freedom House, 1948 March 26 (Box 35:2251)
    - TIME, Inc., 1948 April 16 (Box 35:2252)
    - Shoe Fair, 1948 April 27 (Box 35:2253)
    - "Attitude Research And Some Things it Discloses Today," Krey Dinner Queens College, 1948 May 5 (Box 35:2254)
    - Notes on Marketing/Opinion Research, ca. 1951-1958 (Box 35:2255)
    - Notes on Market Research Pre-Testing, ca. 1951-1958 (Box 36:2256)
    - Commencement Speech, Creston, Iowa/Hebron, 1948 May 20/ 1951 May 16 (Box 36:2257)
    - Bud's Glass Speech, 1948 May (Box 36:2258)
    - "America's Best Export," Sales Executives Club, 1948 June 16 (Box 36:2259)
    - "On the Public Mind," Standard Oil, 1948 October 21 (Box 36:2260)
    - American Meat Institute, 1948 September 22 (Box 36:2261)
    - "The Future of Public Opinion Research," Detroit Economic Club, 1948 December 6 (Box 36:2262)
    - "The Public Looks at Business," Sales Executives Club, 1949 January 5 (Box 36:2263)
    - Cornell University, 1949 April 19 (Box 36:2264)
    - Monclair Forum, 1949 April 21 (Box 36:2265)
    - "The Economic Mood of the American People," Trade Association Executives, 1949 May 19 (Box 36:2266)
    - "Discrimination in Education," Anti-Defamation League, 1949 September 28 (Box 36:2267)
    - "Finding Out What Workers are Thinking," A.M.A., 1949 October 4 (Box 36:2268)
    - Standard Oil Public Relations, 1949 November 21 (Box 36:2269)
    - "World Government," Brooklyn Rotary, 1949 November 2 (Box 36:2270)
    - Analysis of Automobile Industry, ca. 1950 (Box 36:2271)
    - "The Cost of Prejudice to Business," Roosevelt College, 1950 April 20 (Box 36:2272)
    - "Why I'm a New Dealer," Spiegel Ten Year Club, 1950 February 15 (Box 36:2273)
    - "Finding Out What Womekers are Thinking," Atomic Energy Commission, 1950 March 20 (Box 36:2274)
    - "World Government," Bridgeport Rotary, 1950 March 21 (Box 36:2275)
    - "The Welfare State," Mademoiselle College Forum, 1950 April 15 (Box 36:2276)
    - "World Government," American Bar Association, 1950 May 12 (Box 36:2277)
    - American Association for Public Opinion Research (AAPOR), 1950 June 18 (Box 36:2278)
    - "Cost of Discrimination," 1950 May 24 (Box 36:2279)
    - "World Government," NAtional Association of Cost Accountants, 1950 May 31 (Box 36:2280)
    - "Consumer Outlook," 1950 June 20 (Box 36:2281)
    - Cereal Institute, 1950 October 24 (Box 36:2282)
    - "World Government," Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1950 Novmber 15 (Box 36:2283)
    - World Affairs Council, 1951 February (Box 36:2284)
    - New York Baord of Trade and Beta Gamma Sigma Initiation [City College], 1951 (Box 36:2285)
    - New School for Social Research, 1951 April 26 (Box 36:2286)
    - Hebron High School Commencement, 1951 May 16 (Box 36:2287)
    - Atlantic Union Committee, 1951 May 28 (Box 36:2288)
    - "What do We Need Salesmen For?", National Sales Executives 1951 May 31 (Box 36:2289)
    - "Things We've Learned that Copy Researchers Might Profit By," Copy Research Council, 1951 October 30 (Box 36:2290)
    - "What We Already Know About Women," Women's Day Sales Meeting, 1951 November 5 (Box 36:2291)
    - "Inflamatory and Deflationary Forces at Work Today," Life Underwriters Association, 1951 November 8 (Box 36:2292)
    - Public Relations Working Conference, Standard Oil, 1951 November 26 (Box 36:2293)
    - Atlantic Union Committee, 1951 November (Box 36:2294)
    - Atlantic Union Committee, 1952 January 22 (Box 36:2295)
    - Speech, 1952 Janaury 23 (Box 36:2296)
    - Atlantic Union Committee, 1952 January (Box 36:2297)
    - "Politics and Economics (draft), 1952 February (Box 36:2298)
    - Mock Convention, Purdue University, 1952 May 6 (Box 36:2299)
    - Atlantic Union Committee, 1952 May 14 (Box 36:2300)
    - University of Pennsylvania Clubs, 1952 October 9 (Box 36:2301)
    - New York Herald Tribune Forum, 1952 October 21 (Box 36:2302)
    - Cereal Institute, 1952 September 30 (Box 36:2303)
    - "Importance of Advertising" (draft), 1952 (Box 36:2304)
    - "Consumer Behavior" (draft), 1952 (Box 36:2305)
    - Book Paper Manufacturers, 1953 January 20 (Box 36:2306)
    - "Agriculture's Public Relations Problem," National Institute of Animal Agriculture, 1953 April 21 (Box 36:2307)
    - Atlantic Union Committee, 1953 May (Box 37:2308)
    - Direct Mail Association, 1953 September 30 (Box 37:2309)
    - American Meat Institute, 1953 October 5 (Box 37:2310)
    - Bridgeport Association for the United Nations, 1953 October 20 (Box 37:2311)
    - Office Equipment Manufacturers Institute, 1953 November 5 (Box 37:2312)
    - Commonwealth Club of San Francisco, California, 1954 February 19 (Box 37:2313)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1954 June 3 (Box 37:2314)
    - "Other People;s Motives," 1954 (Box 37:2315)
    - Swift and Company, 1955 March 5 (Box 37:2316)
    - "The Problem of External Communications...", Drake University, 1955 March 8 (Box 37:2317)
    - "What the 1954 Elections Portend for 1956," New York Chamber of Commerce, 1955 April 7 (Box 37:2318)
    - Freedom House Forum, 1955 April 8 (Box 37:2319)
    - Atlantic Union Committee, Senate Foreign Relations Committee Testimony, 1955 July 25 (Box 37:2320)
    - National Meat Canners Association on Public Opinion Research, 1955 September 9 (Box 37:2321)
    - U.S. Brewer Foundation, 1956 January 18 (Box 37:2322)
    - Young Men's Business Club, 1956 January 18 (Box 37:2323)
    - Atlantic Union Dinner (not used), 1956 January 25 (Box 37:2324)
    - "Women's Buying Power," College of New Rochelle, 1956 OCtober 13 (Box 37:2325)
    - Atlantic Union Committee (never given), 1956 December (Box 37:2326)
    - Election Polling Speech (used many times), 1956 (Box 37:2327)
    - Fund for the Republic, 1956 February 21 (Box 37:2328)
    - National Civil Liberties Clearing House [see League of Women Voters October 1957], 1957 April 4 (Box 37:2329)
    - A.M.A. Chapter, Columbia University, 1957 April 9 (Box 37:2330)
    - Buffalo Chamber of Commerce, 1957 April 10 (Box 37:2331)
    - Hebron High School, 1957 May 22 (Box 37:2332)
    - Columbia University, 1957 May 30 (Box 37:2333)
    - American Management Association, 1957 June 4 (Box 37:2334)
    - Commission Against Discrimination, 1957 June 11 (Box 37:2335)
    - Robert E. Sherwood Award Luncheon, 1957 June 19 (Box 37:2336)
    - Air Force Information Seminar, 1957 October 10 (Box 37:2337)
    - "Our Ten Year Search for Security and Liberty, 1947-1957," League of Women Voters, 1957 October 10 (Box 37:2338)
    - Men's Career Conference, Oberlin COllege [see Harvard 1960], 1957 December 6 (Box 37:2339)
    - National Society for Business Budgeting and Inplant Food Management, 1958 May (Box 37:2340)
    - Wilton Parent Teacher Association, 1959 February 19 (Box 37:2341)
    - Speech on Social Security, War, Unemployment, ca. 1951-1958 (Box 37:2342)
    - "On Economy and Advertising" [draft], ca. 1951-1958 (Box 37:2343)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration, Harvard University, 1960 October 4 (Box 37:2344)
    - "Foreign Affairs and the Election" (never given), 1960 December (Box 37:2345)
    - "Early Days of the Profession," Bronx High School, 1963 May 2 (Box 37:2346)
    - Election (incomplete notes), 1964 (Box 37:2347)
    - Post-Election, 1964 (Box 37:2348)
    - "Advertising in the 1970s," New School for Social Research, 1965 January 6 (Box 37:2349)
    - "Federalists," Western Electric, 1965 April 15 (Box 37:2350)
    - "The Political Future of the Atlantic World," AFL-CIO International Affairs Conference, 1965 April 23 (Box 37:2351)
    - "The Politics of Three Decades," American Association for Public Opinion Research (AAPOR), 1965 May 24 (Box 37:2352)
    - "Federation: America's Contribution to the World," Sons of the Revolution, 1965 December 4 (Box 37:2353)
    - "Political Future of the Atlantic Union," (draft of speech of same name), AFL-CIO International Conference, 1965 (Box 37:2354)
    - Hoffman Dinner, Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1966 September 29 (Box 37:2355)
    - Senate Resolution 128--Church Resolution, Senate Foreign Relations Committee, 1966 March 23-24 (Box 38:2356)
    - "The Problem of the Atlantic," Cleveland Council on World Affairs, 1966 October 12 (Box 38:2357)
    - Market Research Council, 1967 January 25 (Box 36:2358)
    - NPA and Center for Study of Priority Analysis, 1967 January 27 (Box 38:2359)
    - Sugar Foundation, 1967 February 8 (Box 38:2360)
    - Media Measurement, School of Journalism, Columbia University, 1967 March 9 (Box 38:2361)
    - Presentation for the Bourbon Institute, 1967 April 12 (Box 38:2362)
    - "Your Public of Tomorrow," Life Insurance Agency Management Association, 1967 April 28 (Box 38:2363)
    - "The Urgent New Dimension of Conservation," Nebraska Conservation Conference, 1967 September 18 (Box 38:2364)
    - "Order and Public Opinion," Military Chaplins Association, 1968 April 25 (Box 38:2365)
    - American Management Association, 1968 September 26 (Box 38:2366)
    - Standard Oil of New Jersey (corrected for Hugh Bullock Forum), 1968 October 1 (Box 38:2367)
    - Hugh Bullock Forum, 1968 October 22 (Box 38:2368)
    - "The World of Tomorrow," LIAMA and Metopolitan Life Insurance COmpany, 1968-1969 (Box 38:2369)
    - "Federalists," Western Electric, 1969 March 18 (Box 38:2370)
    - Remarks at the Dedication of Arboretum, University of Nebraska, 1969 June 8 (Box 38:2371)
    - Senator Eugene McCarthy, 1969 (Box 38:2372)
    - Opinion Research, ca. 1967-1969 (Box 38:2373)
    - Turnout, ca. 1967-1969 (Box 38:2374)
    - Lists of Speeches and Articles, undated (Box 38:2375)
  - Subseries B: Notes and Polls, 1936-1969
    - Analysis of Fortune Surveys, ca. 1945-1946 (Box 65:2671)
    - Fortune Polls
      - After the War, 1941-1943 (Box 65:2672)
      - Attitudes Towards Wealth, 1939-1944 (Box 65:2673)
      - Elections, 1936-1944 (Box 65:2674)
      - Evaluation of Roosevelt and his Aims, 1938-1945 (Box 65:2675)
      - Government Regulation--Farmers and Factory Workers, 1938-1942 (Box 65:2676)
      - Russia, 1943-1946 (Box 65:2677)
    - Indepth Interview--Meat--Economist and former high government official, ca. 1951-1958 (Box 65:2678)
    - Indepth Interview--Rubber Industry--Economist and Economist and ex-bureaucrat, ca. 1951-1958 (Box 65:2679)
    - Notes--AT&T Merchandising Seminar, 1956 (Box 65:2680)
    - Notes--Government Regulation, ca. 1967-1969 (Box 65:2681)
    - Pittsburgh National Bank Presentation, 1965 (Box 65:2682)
    - Polls
      - Domestic and International Issues, Economics, 1946 (Box 65:2683)
      - Economics, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 65:2684)
      - Government Regulation, 1936-1944 (Box 65:2685)
      - Iran and Oil Companies (see Standard Oil Public Relations Working Conference), 1951 (Box 65:2686)
      - Likelihood of War and about Truman, ca. 1951 (Box 65:2687)
      - Redding Library, 1952 May 16 (Box 65:2688)
    - Research into Research Presentation (Ford), 1953 (Box 65:2689)
- Series IV: Radio and Television, n.s., 1940-1956
  - "Roosevelt Polls," Tex McCrary Broadcast, 1947 June (Box 38:2376)
  - Questions used on Mrs. Roosevelt's Program re: Atlantic Union Committee, 1951 August (Box 38:2377)
  - Columbia Broadcast System (CBS)
    - 1940 November 1 (Box 38:2378)
    - 1940 November 5 (Box 38:2379)
    - "Who is Complacent?" 1942 May 3 (Box 38:2380)
    - 1948 February (Box 38:2381)
    - 1948 March (Box 38:2382)
    - 1948 April (Box 38:2383)
    - 1948 May (Box 38:2384)
    - 1948 June (Box 38:2385)
    - 1948 July (Box 38:2386)
    - 1948 August (Box 38:2387)
    - 1948 September (Box 38:2388)
    - 1948 October (Box 38:2389)
    - 1948 November (Box 38:2390)
    - 1948 December (Box 38:2391)
    - 1949 January (Box 38:2392)
    - 1949 February (Box 38:2393)
    - 1949 March (Box 38:2394)
    - 1949 April (Box 38:2395)
    - 1949 May (Box 38:2396)
    - 1949 June (Box 38:2397)
    - 1949 July (Box 38:2398)
    - 1949 August (Box 38:2399)
    - 1949 September (Box 38:2400)
    - 1949 October (Box 38:2401)
    - 1949 November (Box 38:2402)
    - 1949 December (Box 38:2403)
    - 1950 January (Box 38:2404)
    - 1950 February (Box 38:2405)
    - 1950 March (Box 38:2406)
    - 1950 April (Box 38:2407)
    - 1950 May (Box 38:2408)
    - 1950 June (Box 38:2409)
    - 1950 July (Box 38:2410)
    - 1950 August (Box 38:2411)
    - 1950 September (Box 38:2412)
    - 1950 October (Box 38:2413)
    - 1950 November (Box 38:2414)
    - 1950 December (Box 38:2415)
    - 1951 January (Box 38:2416)
    - 1951 March (Box 38:2417)
    - 1951 April (Box 38:2418)
    - 1951 May (Box 38:2419)
    - 1951 June (Box 38:2420)
    - 1951 July (Box 38:2421)
    - 1951 August (Box 38:2422)
    - 1951 August (Box 39:2423)
    - 1951 October (Box 39:2424)
    - 1951 November (Box 39:2425)
    - 1951 December (Box 39:2426)
    - 1952 January (Box 39:2427)
    - Bill Leonard TV Spot, 1954 September 20 (Box 39:2428)
    - "Pick the Winner," Westinghouse Statement, 1956 November 5 (Box 39:2429)
  - National Broadcasting Company (NBC)
    - 1952 February (Box 39:2430)
    - 1952 March (Box 39:2431)
    - 1952 April (Box 39:2432)
    - 1952 May (Box 39:2433)
    - 1952 June (Box 39:2434)
    - 1952 July (Box 39:2435)
    - 1952 August (Box 39:2436)
    - 1952 September (Box 39:2437)
    - 1952 October (Box 39:2438)
    - 1952 November (Box 39:2439)
    - "Where the People Stand," TV Show, 1952 November 2 (Box 39:2440)
    - 1952 December (Box 39:2441)
    - 1953 January (Box 39:2442)
    - 1953 February (Box 39:2443)
    - 1953 March (Box 39:2444)
    - 1953 April (Box 39:2445)
    - 1953 May (Box 39:2446)
    - 1953 June (Box 39:2447)
    - 1953 July (Box 39:2448)
    - 1953 August (Box 39:2449)
    - 1953 September (Box 39:2450)
    - 1953 October (Box 39:2451)
    - 1953 November (Box 39:2452)
    - 1953 December (Box 39:2453)
    - 1954 January (Box 39:2454)
- Series V: Jobs, 1953-1961
  - Job 187, Employee Attitude Survey, Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1953 (Box 39:2455)
  - Job 188, Arline Executive Readership Survey, 1953
    - Correspondence (Box 39:2456)
    - Documentation (Box 39:2457)
    - Data (Box 39:2458)
    - Data (Box 40)
  - Job 189, TV Content Analysis, 1953
    - Correspondence (Box 39:2459)
    - Documentation (Box 39:2460)
    - Data--Coding Sheets and instructions (Box 39:2461)
    - Data--Coded Scripts Audio (Box 39:2462-2463)
    - Data--Coded SCripts Video (Box 39:2464-2465)
  - Job 190, Study of Voting Behavior, 1953 (Box 39:2466)
  - Job 191, Texas Wesleyan College Study, 1953-1955
    - Correspondence, 1953 March - April (Box 39:2467)
    - Correspondence, 1953 September - December (Box 39:2468)
    - Correspondence, 1954 January - August (Box 39:2469)
    - Correspondence, 1954 November - 1955 February (Box 39:2470)
    - Documentation--Job details (Box 39:2471)
    - Documentation--Financial data (Box 39:2472)
    - Backgground materials (Box 39:2473-2475)
    - Observations (Box 39:2476-2477)
    - Interviews (Box 39:2478-2491)
    - Data (Box 40)
  - Job 192, Banco Nacional, 1951-1954
    - Correspondence, 1951 March - December (Box 39:2492)
    - Correspondence, 1953 March - September (Box 39:2493)
    - Correspondence, 1953 October - December (Box 39:2494)
    - Correspondence, 1954 January - February (Box 39:2495)
    - Correspondence, 1954 March - April (Box 39:2496)
    - Correspondence, 1954 May - July (Box 39:2497)
    - Data (Box 39:2498)
    - Data (Box 40)
    - Documentation (Box 39:2499)
  - Job 193, Johns Hopkins University subcontract, 1953-1956
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 39:2500)
    - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 39:2501)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 39:2502)
    - Data (Box 40)
    - Documentation (Box 39:2503)
  - Job 194, Italian Election Survey, 1953-1956
    - Correspondence, 1953 May - June (Box 39:2504)
    - Correspondence, 1953 July - August 1956 (Box 39:2505)
    - Data (Box 39:2506)
    - Data (Box 40)
    - Documentation (Box 39:2507)
  - Job 195, Vick Chemical Company, 1953-1954
    - Correspondence, 1953 March - August (Box 42:2508)
    - Correspondence, 1953 September - December (Box 42:2509)
    - Correspondence, 1954 January - October (Box 42:2510)
    - Data (Box 42:2511)
    - Data (Box 40)
    - Documentation (Box 42:2512)
  - Job 196, Industrial Truck Market, 1953
    - Correspondence, 1953 June (Box 42:2513)
    - Correspondence, 1953 July (Box 42:2514)
    - Correspondence, 1953 August (Box 42:2515)
    - Correspondence, 1953 September - December (Box 42:2516)
    - Data (Box 42:2517)
    - Data (Box 40)
    - Documentation--Background materials (Box 42:2518-2519)
    - Documentation--Financial calculations (Box 42:2520)
  - Job 197, ABC Study, 1950-1955
    - Correspondence, 1950 July - !953 February (Box 42:2521)
    - Correspondence, 1953 March - June (Box 42:2522)
    - Correspondence, 1953 July - August (Box 42:2523)
    - Correspondence, 1953 September (Box 42:2524)
    - Correspondence, 1953 October (Box 42:2525-2526)
    - Correspondence, 1953 November (Box 42:2527-2528)
    - Correspondence, 1953 December (Box 42:2529-2530)
    - Correspondence, 1954 January (Box 42:2531)
    - Correspondence, 1954 February - March (Box 42:2532)
    - Correspondence, 1954 April - June (Box 42:2533)
    - Correspondence, 1954 July - October (Box 42:2534)
    - Correspondence, 1955 January - August (Box 42:2535)
    - Data (Box 40)
    - Data--Airmen survey coding instructions (Box 42:2536-2537)
    - Data--Airmen intensive interviews (Box 42:2538-2539)
    - Data--Airmen survey with data (Box 42:2540)
    - Data--French survey coding instructions (Box 42:2541-2542)
    - Data--French survey (Box 42:2543)
    - Data--Reports (Box 42:2544-2545)
    - Documentation--Background materials (Box 42:2546-2548)
    - Documentation--Financial calculations (Box 42:2549)
    - Contract (Box 42:2550)
    - Documentation--Progress Reports, 1953 October - December (Box 42:2551)
    - Documentation--Progress Reports, 1954 January (Box 42:2552)
    - Documentation--Proposal (Box 42:2553)
  - Job 199, Manufacturing Executives,1953
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 42:2554)
    - Data (Box 40)
    - Documentation (Box 42:2555)
  - Job 201, United States Information Agency, 1953
    - Correspondence (Box 42:2556)
    - Data (Box 40)
    - Data--Code sheets (Box 42:2557-2559)
    - Data-- Report drafts (Box 42:2560-2561)
    - Documentation--Background materials (Box 42:2562-2563)
    - Documentation--Financial calculations (Box 42:2564)
  - Job 202, Mass Media/Latin America, 1953
    - Correspondence (Box 43:2565)
    - Data (Box 40)
    - Data--Data sheets (Box 43:2566-2567)
    - Data--Report (Box 43:2568-2572)
    - Documentation--Background information (Box 43:2573)
    - Documentation--Financial calculations (Box 43:2574)
  - Job 203, Extension of Job 178 (Chile), 1954
    - Correspondence (Box 43:2575)
    - Data (Box 40)
    - Documentation (Box 43:2576)
  - Job 204, United States Information Agency Refugee Study, 1952-1956
    - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 43:2577)
    - Correspondence, 1953 February - March (Box 43:2578)
    - Correspondence, 1953 April - November (Box 43:2579)
    - Correspondence, 1954 January - May (Box 43:2580)
    - Correspondence, 1954 June - November (Box 43:2581)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 43:2582)
    - Documentation--Background materials (Box 43:2583)
    - Documentation--Financial calculations (Box 43:2584)
    - Documentation--Proposals/contracts (Box 43:2585)
  - Job 299, Magazine Advertising Survey, 1958
    - Correspondence, 1958 April - May (Box 43:2586)
    - Correspondence, 1958 May (Box 43:2587)
    - Correspondence, 1958 June (Box 43:2588-2590)
    - Correspondence, 1958 July (Box 43:2591)
    - Data (Box 40)
    - Documentation--Coding instructions/daily reports (Box 43:2592)
    - Documentation--Surveys/reports (Box 43:2593)
  - Job 300, United States Information Agency; Richard Nixon Survey, 1958
    - Correspondence, 1958 May (Box 43:2594)
    - Correspondence, 1958 June - September (Box 43:2595)
    - Data (Box 40)
    - Documentation (Box 43:2596)
  - Job 301, Richard Nixon trip, 1958-1959
    - Correspondence, 1958 May (Box 43:2597)
    - Correspondence, 1958 June (Box 43:2598-2599)
    - Correspondence, 1958 June - 1959 January (Box 43:2600)
    - Data (Box 40)
    - Data--Report (Box 43:2601)
    - Data--Responses (Box 43:2602)
    - Documentation (Box 43:2603)
  - Job 302, Citizenship Survey, 1957-1961
    - Correspondence--Client, 1957 - 1958 July (Box 43:2604)
    - Correspondence--Client, 1958 August - December (Box 43:2605)
    - Correspondence--Client, 1959 January - April (Box 43:2606)
    - Correspondence--Client, 1959 May - July (Box 43:2607)
    - Correspondence, 1959 August - September (Box 43:2608)
    - Correspondence--Client, 1959 October - December (Box 43:2609)
    - Correspondence--Client, 1960 January - March (Box 43:2610)